# ISHWAAN.

# **OBJECTIVE**

A challenging growth-oriented position in a progressive company where I could contribute to the organization's success not only by my technical expertise but also through my innovative ideas and desire to achieve excellence in whatever I do.

#### **SKILLS**

(Production support, Service-analyst, Technical Analyst, Application support, Api & integration support) Working in PRODUCTION and UAT environment

Experienced in managing application build & implementing file-based integration. Concepts of Pods, Nodes, containerization, Deployments, Version build, Continuous monitoring,

Hands on Experience on managing application deployment and support on Azure cloud environment with docker Kubernetes based deployment architecture.

Experience on working tools like, WINSCP, KIBANA, GRIFANA, TRELLO, ,JIRA, SUMMIT, DYNATRACE And Knowledge of SQL Query & databsase. PL/SQL, ORACLE

Good knowledge of implementing DML, DDL, TCL, DCL, Languages Knowledge of ITIL and incident & Problem management change Management & Application management And support.

Organizational support & Skill to provide Support on management.

Basic understanding on Audit & Application compliance

Good understanding on API & Integrations within the Application.

Assisting & supporting Team to reach there service goals

Managing & supporting to get the task to the closure.

Analyzing on ops gaps and provide Support to the teams to close within the TAT

Creating Incidents and tickets within the SLA and closing the Tickets by Ticketing system

Having ability to manage Production / Application Support to various Live Applications Knowledge

Real-time monitoring & analysis of call logs.

## **Technical Analyst**

## Avenues Payments PVT LTD (FABLE FINTECH), February 2022 – Till

Now PROJECT: ICICI ORP (client) PRODUCTION SUPPORT/Application support

Digital payment Domain ONE REMITTANCE PLATFORM Uk/Canada/India

- Working on Azure cloud environment. AKS
- Kubernetes based deployment architecture
- Providing support for PAAS component Application, Integrated with azure environment
- Monitor API'S and Integration flow of Request & Response for transactions. manage the uptime of the production systems using Application monitoring tools.
- Experienced in managing application build & implementing file-based integration.
- Providing support in monitoring tools Kibana, Grifana, Dynatrace, servicenow, jiira, trello
- Analyzing Functional and logical issues raised by business and getting resolved with Development & operations teams and ensure that the application is working correctly as deployed
- · Facilitate the transition between project support and production support for all change
- Providing Technical support & Analysis for online transaction processing module
- · Health check and monitoring and log analysis on daily basis.
- Get team analyize before Executing queries in database as per client issues and internal updates.
- · Leading and supporting team for smooth transition of process adhere within the environment
- Coordinate with dev/product team in getting resolution as and when required.
- Provide end to end support to ops users/dev team/icici users
- Keep up with the product releases and learn the functioning of features from time-2-time.
- Responsible for proper knowledge of Prioritization Matrix to classify the incidents and service requests as per the Severity
- Responsible to monitor the Incident status to respond, resolution as per SLA
- Call Escalation as per defined escalation matrix
- Maintaining call reports of users on daily basis

# **Work Experience**

## **IT Service-Analyst**

Xangars Infratech solutions Pvt.Ltd, March 2019 – january 2022

PROJECT: Tataaia Life insurance: B2B(client) PRODUCTION SUPPORT

#### Insurance/Digital payment Domain

- Providing support in Handling oracle database 12c. Backend and front-end website.
- Analyzing Functional and logical issues raised by business and operations getting resolved with Developing teams.
- Technical support for online transaction process
- Application support and Maintenance
- coordinate with dev/ product team in getting resolution as and when required.
- · Provide end to end support to External users
- Making changes in database as per client issues and internal updates.
- Keep up with the product releases and learn the functioning of features from time-2-time. Maintain SLAs to follow smooth transition
- Creating login id and raising ticket, for the same.
- Updating database as per customer and internal requirements
- Responsible for proper knowledge of Prioritization Matrix so as to classify the incidents and service requests as per the Severity
- · Responsible to monitor the Incident status to respond, resolution as per SLA
- Call Escalation as per defined escalation matrix

# **IT** support

#### Modern Informatics Pvt.Ltd, september 2017 – januarary 2019

PROJECT: Infra support

#### Security infra Domain

- Trouble-shooting Hardware, software & Network problems
- Installing Windows 7, 8, 8.1, 10,
- Outlook Configuration 2010,2012,2016 and Backup data of mails
- Configure all types of Printers on USB, Network and WIFI
- Providing remote support to External Employees & clients through (Any desk, Team viewer, Ammyadmin)
- And coordinating with phones and E-mails to resolve the Employees and clients issue
- Installing SQL Server 2012, 2014.
- · Managing Centralized Anti-Virus.
- Configuring & installing of network routers (Tech routers, Saturn) by Remote access
- Daily Backup taken according to the Schedule
- · Maintain asset inventory of Desktops, Laptops, Printers and Phones
- · Creating Tickets within the SLA, And closing the tickets
- Maintaining call reports of users on daily basis

# **Work Experience**

#### **Technical support Engineer**

Agate Business Services Pvt.Ltd, March 2016 – june 2017

PROJECT: Technical Helpdesk (Hpcl Helpdesk) HINDUSTAN PETROLEUM CORPORATION

#### **Procuremnet Domain**

- To handle the web portal of (HINDUSTAN PETROLEUM CORPORATION) site
- Responsible for attending all incidents, service requests landing at the Service Desk via the Helpline Tool, Mail & Telephone.
- And providing (Remote) support to the vendors by (Team viewer, Any desk, Ammy admin)
- · Responsible for understanding the various categories of vendors calls
- Rresponsibilities of the Help Desk Coordinator will be to Log all the calls, assign it to Support Groups, track it till closure, and update the user
- Responsible for allocating proper call categories for the incidents and Service Requests
- Adherence to response time is the key responsibility of SD
- Responsible for proper knowledge of Prioritization Matrix so as to classify the incidents and service requests as per the Severity
- And to monitor the Incident status to respond, resolution as per SLA
- Ensuring proper activity details are updated in tool
- Responsible to inform Shift Lead & Manager in case Incident is violated or going to violate the SLA
- · Generate daily, weekly & monthly reports

# **Technical support executive**

Altius Pvt.Ltd, september 2014 – october 2015

PROJECT: Technical support (Marico tech Support) MARICO

#### **FMCG Domain**

- Troubleshooting & Maintenance of Sql based Application (Midas) App(General trade)
- Sql based Application
- Backup Update of application and app
- Installation and Troubleshooting issue in Application & Apps of vendors
- Trouble shooting of Midas application in both frontend & backend Sql database
- And updating and validating the database.
- Installation antivirus on demand of client.
- · Recovering Data from Media Failures,

# **Education**

Exam Passed	Board/University	Year
B.Tech-COMPUTER SCIENCE	SAISHA INSTITUTE OF TECHNICAL SCIENCE-	2014
HSC-SCIENCE, MATHS	Mumbai Board(SRP JUNIOR COLLEGE) -	2009
SSC-SCIENCE	Tamil nadu Board(DON BOSCO HR SEC SCHO	OOL) - 2007

Phone: (+91) 9029708636

Email:md.ridz636@gmail.com Navi Mumbai-410206

INDIA